Osman..
...look what your greed did to you.
Look at your people's state.
My Bey...
Surely...
...there will be a price for this oppression.
Let her.
Mother..
We might be crying now...
But we will not bow down, my Bey.
Only this suits your people.
As long as we have you...
...this state will never collapse. Thank you.
Walk! Come on walk!
Altuga.
Bring his Hatun and his children.
Bring them, so they'll walk to death together.
They ran away. Commander Ulugan.
They ran away with a few people.
Our nokers(Mongolian Soldiers) are after them.
So they ran away, huh?
Is there a hole in this world which can save
them from Mongols? Why are they even running?
They are just growing the fire
of wrath that's waiting for them.
This is your fate.
You wrote this fate.
I wish you could watch your
Hatun and your little dogs die.
I wish, Osman.
But apparently, death will take you before them.
I will make your cause die.
I will kill everyone from your family!
Nothing will be left behind you, Osman.
Even if you kill me, even
if you kill my children...
...even if you leave no one behind...
...the cause of Turks never die!
Enough!
Ghazi stop! What are you doing?
-Ghazi!
-Stop...
Stop, Cerkutay's dog, stop.
Let go of me, you jackal -My valiant...
The one you are trying to chain is
Osman Bey! He will make you pay for this!
My valiant...
Nokers(Mongolian Soldiers).
Take this one to the tent.
Don't touch me!
-Don't worry...
My Bey...
Don't worry.
Do you see?
A child..
...a Hatun, a man...
There is always someone who
will protect the cause of Turks.
No one can disrupt our unity.
We will see Osman.
We will see.
We will see the situation of people...
...while their Bey is dying in my hands.
Prepare the setup.
Osman will be the target of my arrows.
My Bey!
My Bey, don't!
-My Bey, don't!
-Don't worry.
Don't worry...
Come on! Come on!
We are safe for now.
Have some rest. -Come on.
Orhan..
Sit down.
Don't be afraid.
Help.
Mother... Where is my father?
We learned that he was in Sogut.
We cannot leave my father in those dogs' hands.
We won't. Orhan, Alaeddin.
Orhan, treat his wounds, my son.
-Brother...
Stop, Alaeddin. Wait.
Mother..
My wounds are not important.
My father is.
We will not leave my father
in those dastard dogs' hands.
My Shahzade...
Wear this...
Thank you Samil. -You are not alright...
You are covered in bruises.
I am alright, my Holofira. I
am alright, don't worry. I am...
Ghazi!
Ghazi is not here, Cerkutay!
-Ghazi..
Ghazi?
Ghazi!
Have you seen Ghazi? Ghazi!
He is not here!
Ghazi! Where is Ghazi!
Ulgen! Ulgen, when was
the last time you saw him?
Meryem... He was with Meryem.
Meryem?
Meryem, mother! Meryem is not here!
Did they get caught?
They were right behind us!
Ghazi is not here!
Ghazi!
Turhan Alp! Ghazi is not here!
-Stop... Stop!
Brother, those dogs will kill
you once you arrive in the tribe.
You are walking to fire, brother. Don't!
-I cannot stop, brother!
Ghazi is in the hands of
Mongols! How can I stop?!
Brother! -Cerkutay, stop!
Ghazi is strong and brave.
Besides, that dog named
Altuga would never kill Ghazi.
-I have to go!
-We will find him!
We will find him Cerkutay, we will!
-Brother...
We will find him, don't worry!
-I cannot wait here, my Shahzade!
They will take him from me!
No one will take him! No one!
Cerkutay! Cerkutay!
We will not let this happen.
We will save him from there safe
and sound, like our other people.
But not now, we have to act wisely now!
Bala Hatun! Bala Hatun!
The dastards took Osman Bey to the tribe.
We can see the tribe from the hilltop. Let's go.
Alright. Fatma, Ulgen.
You and Alp take people
to the tents behind Karadin.
It was evacuated before.
Nobody would know. Come on.
Come on, Ulgen. Let's go.
-Let's go to the hilltop.
-Come on.
-We'll save him. Let's go.
-Come on, come on.
Come on.
Impertinent Bey of Kayi.
Your sons who ran away...
While I kill them.
...I won't be as merciful as I'm to you.
Come on.
Untie my hands.
Grab your sword and fight me.
Fight me if you have courage.
So I can show you what the frontiers are.
So I can return your cruelty.
No.
Killing you like a soldier would a gift for you.
You will fall in weakness.
Yusuf, they'll kill Osman Bey.
They'll murder him vilely.
Dastards! Dogs!
If my Bey is killed.
...then Kayi will make your lives miserable!
With Allah's will, they will! Dastards!
Dastards! Dastards!
Release our Bey, tyrants!
You've tortured enough!
You and your people, even in this situation.
...never lose your courage.
This courage will destroy...
...you and all of your
people who rise with cruelty!
Where did they take Ghazi, Meryem?
They won't harm Ghazi, will they?
-They won't hurt him.
-Don't worry, Ayse.
He will be fine.
My father must have left with Bala Hatun.
But I know... He's going to save us.
Look, Osman. The last guests
you'll host in your tribe are coming.
Vile dogs!
You didn't only enter the wolf's tent...
...but also took your jackals with you, huh?
You always take the smell
of the feast and arrive in time!
You execute the bey of Kayi..
...and we miss the show?
Not in this world.
Vile dog!
Well..
Where is Bala?
She will be the next.
As long as I keep breathing,
...you will be the next ones to die.
You will die too.
Inglorious Sofia!
You'll die too! Don't worry!
Osman.
Before I kill you
...there is something I want to show you.
Bring him.
Vile dastards!
-Lukas...
You'll see.
We will make you pay.
Ilbay.
What are you doing there?
Not only Ilbay.
You should know the man on your chair.
The new Bey of Kayi.
Ilbay Bey, grandson of Sungur Tegin.
What?
Leave me.
My... My uncle...
...Sungur Tegin's grandson, huh?
You heard right, Osman.
I'm the grandson of Sungur Tegin...
...who made great efforts
for the future of Turks.
And you, Begum Hatun?
-I am...
Begum Hatun...
...is my wife-to-be.
Don't look at me like that, Osman.
This is divine justice.
This is the day when the
right will regain his rights.
Is that...
Is that why you stayed with me for so long?
Did you think this was your right?
You were dreaming of this throne, huh?
Is that why...
...you worked with these
dogs and came close to me?
I don't want anything else
but what is mine, Osman.
My grandfather Sungur Tegin Bey...
...was a warrior who sacrificed
his title and life for Kayi.
-This chair has always been my right!
-Shut up!
You see, Lukas?
I told you Ilbay was more than he looked.
A dagger that Osman trusted so
much and that stuck into his heart.
You dastard.
You..
You let all these dogs in the state tent...
...and you say you are Kayi
While all our people are tortured outside!
Don't you have any honor?
Don't you have any dignity at all?
Know your...
All these people here...
...are the new masters and allies of Kayi.
The new head of Kayi is Ilbay.
Kayi belongs to Mongolians now.
Your alps, people and everyone else...
...are servants of Mongolians now.
Turks can never be dominated.
They will! It will be whatever I say!
Sofia and Lukas are...
...Kayi's allies from now on.
Your cryings of conquest have brought nothing
but blood and death in these lands, Osman.
I will do just the opposite and
take a good care of my people.
I will help this glorious state...
...reach peace and rest.
What you will reach will
be only captivity and defeat.
You'll never be worthy of...
...my uncle Sungur Tegin or Kayi.
-I won't leave you to them, Osman.
-Here they are!
-Behind the trees!
-Come here.
They're approaching.
We'll strike them like
lightnings with our swords!
Boran Bey, shoot your arrows!
Kill those dogs running to their death!
-Are you alright?
-I'm good.
Orhan, you aren't well.
Look, your wound hurts my heart. You stay back.
-We can handle this.
-I'm good, Holofira.
Before my father is saved
from those Mongolian dogs,
...my wound is my fellow.
Orhan..
-I am... Holofira.
Gonca, you stay with Holofira.
-She's carrying a baby.
-I'll look after them. Don't worry.
-Come on, come on.
-Allah is the greatest!
-Come on!
-Come on.
Come on.
Why do you love cruel Osman so much?
Let our Bey go!
You should all learn a lesson
from the things you will see here.
See what Mongols do to those who oppose
and what they offer to those who obey.
While Osman is going to
death, greet the new Bey of Kayi.
New Kayi Bey?
New Kayi Bey is Sungur
Tekin's grandson Ilbay Bey!
Ilbay? Traitor Ilbay!
Father..
Is Ilbay a Kayi?
What did you do, father?
Begum Hatun..
Sister... Sister, what are you trying to do?
-Traitor...
Dastards..
Before we kill one of these
dogs, the others come!
Ulugan dog sent his dogs everywhere!
We will not stop even if
there is shahada in the end!
Dastard dog!
Now, your people who are begging to save you...
...will soon obey Mongols and
remember you as a traitor, Osman.
Oghuz' blessed lineage never
bows down to you or dogs like you.
Those like you can only find
peace by dying on these lands.
I know how to turn that
blessed people into sheep.
Nokers(Mongolian Soldiers).
Tie Osman Bey up. Tie him up tightly.
Come on!
We will now understand what these dogs want!
Come on, to the hill! Come on!
-Come on!
Come on!
See the end of the one who
stood against the Mongols.
This will be a lesson to everyone.
O, my suffering people...
...who resists every hardship.
Why are we still letting him speak?
-Let him speak...
It's his last words anyway.
I will never forgive you, father.
Lift your head.
Lift your head
We will always stand tall!
Even if they shed our blood...
...even if they bury our bodies...
...they will never gain a victory.
You will never...
...cry after me!
You will not lose your hope!
Even if I die...
You will forever follow and
protect my ever-lasting da'wah.
Now those who put us into this
situation must know, even if I die...
...those who will come after me
will never bow down to captivity!
Who can make Turks who are in
love with The Righteous and freedom kneel?
You are at the end of the way, Osman.
Even when he is at the
end, he is still ambitious.
I will rip your heart out.
I bear witness that there is none
worthy of worship except Allah...
...and I bear witness that Muhammad(PBUH)
is His servant and Messenger.
Who dares to do that? Who?!
Who is trying to save
Osman's life? Show yourself!
Thanks to Allah..
Who is that?
It's a messenger.
Mongol messenger.
It's Olcaytu Khan...
...who saved Osman's life.
Olcaytu Khan, huh?
Why did our Khan..
...stop Osman's execution?
Only our Khan knows that. He ordered...
...Osman to be taken to Tabriz immediately.
How is this possible, Ulugan?
It is possible if Olcaytu Khan orders so.
Altuga, prepare the caged cart.
You will take him there.
Nokers(Mongolian Soldiers),
you heard the commander...
My Allah..
You are the Greatest.
Now...
...since this heart is
still beating in this body...
...you are the ones who should be afraid.
Do not forget who you are going to see, Osman.
If there is someone..
...who needs to be afraid, that's you.
They are bringing the caged
cart. They will go somewhere.
We know where they will take him.
Either to the Mongol palace...
...or the Mongol lands.
You are right, brother.
Only Olcaytu...
...can stop Ulugan.
My Osman Bey! My Osman Bey!
Don't cry...
My father betrayed you, my Osman Bey.
He betrayed your lineage. -No...
As long as we have brave warriors like you...
...traitors among us won't be able to upset us.
Ayse...
Ayse. Come on. Go.
My daughter, come here. -Don't touch me.
Put him in the cart.
My Allah helped us. Our Bey is alive.
Now we need to save him.
This is our duty.
But there are too many of them.
Nokers(Mongolian Soldiers)
are forming a line.
When they leave the tribe, we
can trap them in the narrow valley.
Then we will have the advantage.
We will open the door of that cage.
No matter what it costs, we
will open the door of that cage.
We cannot go there on foot.
We need horses.
You are right.
Turhan. Alps.
Find horses immediately.
-As you order.
Today, everything is for our state.
Osman Bey's struggle is our struggle.
May Allah help us.
-Aameen. -Aameen.
Come on, get ready.
Altuga, convey my respects to our Khan.
Set our Bey free!
Traitors! -Don't touch me!
Even if it is Olcaytu Khan's order,
...it's not right to leave Osman
alive, Commander Ulugan.
Are you afraid of his power...
...as long as he keeps breathing?
Don't be.
We will make only our own power rule you.
Ilbay is right, Ulugan.
You should have killed
Osman while you had a chance.
Bala, Orhan... They're all missing.
They will never stop following Osman.
That's what I want, hatun.
Let them attempt to reach Osman.
They will be my preys.
Sister.
What have you done?
How could you betray Osman Bey, sister?
We'll talk, brother.
Release Yusuf Bey. He's
Ilbay Bey's brother-in-law.
What are you talking about, sister?
I already knew your nature, Begum Hatun!
You are a traitor!
Traitor.
What have you done, sister?
What have you done?
You didn't die but you will
taste even much worse in Tabriz.
You'll never be able to come back to your tribe.
My bird.
Thank God, you're fine.
My aunt.
I missed you so much.
-Look.
Thanks to you, Osman's reign is over.
Kayi people are just a broken herd now.
Aunt...
Mongolians killed too many people.
They left many orphans behind.
Osman is a bad man. That's right.
But he's a good leader, aunt.
Are you defending Osman, Poena?
The man who slaughtered
your parents mercilessly.
The man who left you alone
among the dead bodies.
If your parents heard this.
..they would die once again due to sorrow.
Osman..
...tortured them to death.
I'm sorry, aunt.
They acted so sincerely to me...
Osman and Bala acted warmly to you, didn't they?
You thought they cared for you.
Well..
This is their biggest weapon.
And you...
...got deceived by their
fake faces, my little bird.
They never cared for you. They just pitied.
When I got poisoned,
...Osman and Bala looked
after me as if I were their family.
Osman said he would protect me, aunt.
Well, Poena...
Their words are poisonous.
They put you in this situation. Look.
All alone.
A lonely kid.
Remember your hatred.
Remember your parents.
Crying doesn't suit you at all.
You're right, aunt.
You're right.
I was deceived by their tricks.
Today is the vengeance day.
Go after Osman and kill him.
Osman has to die for your
parents to rest in peace.
You have my word.
I promise I will kill you aunt.
I'm sure you will succeed.
Aunt, I want Osman's horse.
I will ride on him.
Can you control him?
Mongolians always use this route.
And their nokers(Mongolian Soldiers)
take positions in these spots.
You say they will go through
this, right, my Shahzade?
We need to catch up before
they get out of our borders.
Then we need to use the short cut quickly...
...and ambush them on the way.
Before they get out of borders,
we will take Osman Bey back.
God willing.
May Allah help us all.
-Aameen.
Here we go!
Come on
What's going on here?
Bala Hatun's horse is bad tempered.
It's trying to run off.
Alaca, do you want to go to Bala?
Bala just abandoned you, though.
Don't be upset.
You will be my horse, alright?
Don't try in vain.
She lets nobody else but Bala.
She's loyal to her owner.
I will cut off..
...people and this horse's loyalty to Bala.
They will even forget Bala's name.
And you?
Can you take Osman's place?
I'm not impatient like you.
I'm waiting for my time.
Osman will vanish when it's time.
And my reign will begin.
I will be such a bey to them that
they won't even remember Osman.
Osman is alive, though.
What if he comes back?
What if he makes you pay for what you did?
What?
Are you afraid?
I'm afraid of nothing, Ilbay.
But I always pick my way.
Osman isn't a wolf that you can hold in a cage.
Don't worry, hatun.
Osman will never be able to come back.
If he does, I will kill him myself.
How much further?
There is a stream ahead that feeds the river.
We should take a rest there
before we get out of the borders.
Your words mean nothing here, Osman.
We will have some rest wherever I want.
Well..
Whoever ignores the right words
will hit their heads to the stones!
Nobody else knows this area better than I do.
Yes. You know it well enough
that you can play tricks in it.
What?
Are you afraid of me?
I'm not afraid of you.
I just pity you, Osman.
You still have hopes for
running away but you can't.
I will break your hopes like
the wounds I made in your body.
A Turk is always hope against the dark.
We know how to make the cruel kneel.
Just be patient.
My captivity will be over soon.
Then you will see the dark.
Don't be so sure, Osman. Do not be so sure.
I heard you love Osman, Iltutan...
But I will kill him today.
I know, you..
...think he is a good man. But he is a murderer!
He killed my family, Iltutan!
So you will be an orphan. But don't worry.
I'll take care of you better than him.
Let's go and find Osman.
Sister, isn't that Ilbay a traitor?
Didn't he fool us? Didn't he betray Osman Bey?
How can you say you'll marry him?
-Betrayal for whom, Yusuf?
Ilbay is a Kayi who was treated unfairly.
And he cares about the people more than him.
Sister, what did he say to you?
How did he convince you? How did he trick you?
No one can trick me!
No one can put pressure on me!
We came here with our huge Beylic
and pledged allegiance to Osman.
His impertinent Hatun, Bala
humiliated me and sent me away!
If there is a betrayal, it is
what Osman and his Hatun did.
Sister, look, I am afraid
your grudge will hurt you.
When Osman Bey gets the chair back...
That won't happen.
While I rule state after I marry Ilbay...
...you will grow our Beylic.
Be smart, Yusuf.
I am doing everything for both of us.
Your way is my way, sister.
I will always be by your side
Brother..
Now!
The Righteous!
My Bey..
Osman..
My Bey! My Bey!
Trap!
Trap! Be careful!
Bala!
You found your death while looking for Osman..
Red devil..
You will die before Osman.
Dastard dogs... We will ruin...
...the game you planned here!
We will never fall before
we kill you! Come on Alps!
Allah is the Greatest!
Do not resist for no reason, Bala.
We have a long way to go, Osman.
If you sit there and behave...
...I will take you to Tabriz
without treating you like a dog.
But if you do... -Shut up
Altuga or something...
I will rip that tongue out of your throat.
Osman..
They said you were stubborn.
Look, you lost your state,
but you are still stubborn.
You are a Bey who follows customs. But..
..it's over now.
Ulu Shaman...
...play your qopuz.
Let's make Osman Bey a little happy.
Dog!
What is it?
Did I hurt you?
You dog..
Are you scared?
I told you not to speak!
Of course you are scared,
you are facing Osman Bey!
As long as we have brave warriors like you...
...traitors among us cannot upset us.
This is the dagger of my
grandfather Sungur Tekin...
Thank you Ayse. Thank you.
Osman is running away!
Come on! Catch him!
You say the same thing every
time my sword touches yours.
But I will not die before I kill you.
You will not die easily, Bala.
You will beg me.
Did that hurt?
Are you still planning games?
It is the only truth of your life!
We are stepping back! Come on!
Attack!
-Don't let them run away!
-They won't be able to escape! Attack!
You will never be able to escape, Osman.
Never.
So you ran away Osman... But I swear...
..I will kill you.
Noker(Mongolian Soldiers) Uncle.
I am Ilbay Bey's daughter.
I am giving everyone sherbet
because my father is the new Bey.
Drink some.
Ghazi.
I know I am late...
But I could not come before.
Did you know your father was a traitor, Ayse?
Stop..
Let's untie this knot. We have to escape.
You always told me "If you knew who I was..."..
This was why, right?
You knew you were a Kayi
I knew it.
But I did not know my
father was a traitor, Ghazi.
If I knew, wouldn't I tell
you and our Osman Bey?
You are far away from your father
and mother because of my father.
I will not get mad at you
even if you don't believe me.
It's not about my father or mother, Ayse.
We are losing our state.
We need to save Osman Bey, come on.
Before they took my Osman
Bey, I secretly gave him a dagger.
So maybe he could save himself.
Halal to you Ayse.
I swear you will be a brave Alp.
I will not be an Alp!
I will be a Sister!
Like Bala Hatun.
Come on.
We must escape before the effect
of the sherbet wears off. Let's go!
You are right.
Tie Ghazi up.
Ayse will come with me.
Don't touch me!
Let me go!
No! No! Osman Bey will make
you pay for this! Let me go!
Let me go!
Come at us, you infidel dogs.
O Righteous!
Go after them!
No one will survive here!
Go after them
Pick every stone up! Look everywhere
Osman is not far away,
he is around here! Come on!
Where did you hide, Osman?
Where are you? Iltutan, stop! Stop! Iltutan!
Iltutan, be quiet!
Iltutan!
There are tracks here.
This way!
Search everywhere!
Noises come from this side! Come on!
Osman.
So you are here, Osman.
It's over now, Osman.
There is no tomorrow for you.
Today, I am Azrael.
Today is the day of your death.
She is going to Osman!
She is one of Osman's people! Kill her!
Meryem! My daughter!
Come here. Come.
We've put quite a distance between us.
They lost our trail, but we can't stop.
We need to find out which
direction they took Osman Bey.
The real trap must be set along the road.
Mother, only two roads lead to Tabriz now.
The Saricali road is quite
winding, it will slow us down.
Kizilkayalar, on the other hand,
passes through the swamp, Alaeddin.
They must have taken serious
precautions to protect my father.
Why would so many nokers
(Mongolian Soldiers) go through the swamp?
We can no longer be sure
of anything. These devils...
...might have used both routes to mislead us.
The best way is to split
up and search both ways.
That way, we won't lose time either, right?
-You are right my Orhan.
Then, Alaeddin, you and
the girls take the Saricali route.
Turhan will go with you.
Cerkutay will lead us through Kizilkayalar
without taking us into the swamp.
Boran, Aykut, you will come with me.
-As you order Bala Hatun.
-Okay.
Come on! Let's not waste
time! May Allah be with you!
Come on!
Come on
Meryem, what are you doing here?
I ran away from the tribe, my Bey.
I wanted to help you, but I couldn't...
I see. I see.
I understood you were
brave when I first saw you.
Here...
But my Bey... You are also hurt.
I will only slow you down
while Mongols are after us.
Why do you say that?
Is my life more precious than yours? Huh?
-True, but..
...because of the antidote...
You are in this situation because of us.
-Don't worry.
Nothing will happen to us.
Hang on now. I will break the arrow.
Did that hurt a lot?
Yes, my Bey.
Alright.
We need to find herbs to ease your pain.
Come, let's go somewhere hidden.
Come.
My Ayse..
My daughter, why are you doing this?
Because my father taught me honesty and bravery!
Why are you doing this?!
Look, my daughter.
I am doing everything to take what is ours.
I deserve this chair.
And after me, it will belong to your children.
I don't want it.
Those bad men...
Mongols... They kill everyone!
And they are keeping Ghazi as a prisoner!
And they will martyr our Osman Bey!
And you are uniting with
them! And you say it's our right!
Are we going to get what's
ours by betraying others?!
My daughter, this is not betrayal.
What Osman did is actual betrayal.
You don't understand me now.
But when you grow up, you
will say your father was right.
My father?
My father would never let others oppress Turks!
I don't know you!
You are not my father! -My Ayse!
My Bey.
You are the heir of Sungur Tegin.
If a Kayi Bey is to sit on the chair
...it shouldn't be Osman but you.
Even if you don't do it for
yourself, do it for your daughter.
-For the only thing left from your wife.
-Never. The chair is Osman Bey's.
This dagger and little Ayse are enough for me.
I won't betray my kin.
If you don't, I will.
I'm now Ilbay, grandson of Sungur Tegin.
And you are my daughter.
Ayse, my daughter.
We've kept our secret together so far.
We've gone through a lot.
It's all because of Osman.
You asked me why we kept this dagger.
If Osman had known we had the dagger.
...he'd have killed both you and me.
This dagger...
Where is the dagger?
I gave it to Osman Bey.
-So he could save himself.
-What did you do, Ayse?
You've gone too far this time.
Stay here.
I swear...
...I will get those rebels
executed in this square.
They can't go anywhere
now. They are all in need.
They will fall into our claws.
Ulugan.
Osman.
What about him?
My daughter Ayse...
...gave Osman a dagger when she hugged him.
He can't get out of the cage with
the dagger but you should know.
What are you talking about, Ilbay?
Are you hearing yourself?
Just as Osman was going to our Khan,
...your kid gave him a dagger
to help him escape, huh?
If Osman escapes
...my credibility will be
ruined before Olcaytu Khan.
And your head won't stand on your shoulders!
He can't escape while
Altuga is there. Don't worry.
Nokers(Mongolian Soldiers)!
Go warn Altuga to be careful! Now!
If we can't find Osman Ulugan will kill us all!
Search everywhere! Everywhere!
There's blood here.
Blood here!
Osman.
Where are you going, Osman?
You can't go much further
with your wound. Nokers(Mongolian Soldiers)!
Osman will try to spend
the night in an isolated place.
Caves and pits... Leave no stones unturned!
Come, hold on. Come on.
Hold on, hold on.
-We need to find a safe place.
-I can hold on.
Iltutan.
Come here.
My Iltutan.
What are you doing here?
I brought Iltutan here, my Bey.
-But we got separated.
-What?
How come?
How could he let you ride him?
I don't know.
He didn't show bad temper.
Iltutan..
He wouldn't let anyone ride him.
Look at me.
Iltutan.
Well... He knows where to stop and who to help.
Come on, let's go.
We need to find a safe place.
Come on.
Mongolian dastards always leave tracks behind.
But there are no tracks here.
Ulugan isn't like the ones we saw before.
He's not. We need to be cautious.
We will either find a way or make our own way.
But we have to save Osman Bey somehow.
Orhan. Let me check your wound.
It's not a big deal,
Holofira. I'm good.
You're not.
Brother, let's have some
rest. We can't go on like this.
We should examine your wounds.
I'll spread this ointment on your wounds.
I will do it.
Alright.
-Come on.
-Ayaz! Yagiz!
Watch around.
-We'll take some rest and continue.
-As you order, my Bey.
You will be alright.
Holofira, this wound...
It's nothing.
My father...
...was taken captive...
...to save me because of me.
This wound is nothing
compared to the fire inside me.
We'll save father and take our tribe back.
Beyond believing, I'm sure of this.
Just like I knew you'd come back.
God willing, Holofira.
God willing.
We will heal all our wounds.
God gave us
...such a gift in such a time.
It means hope.
It's a message.
Holofira.
My Holofira.
My daylight... My sun.
Is this... Do I get it right?
-I am...
You're going to be a father.
I'm pregnant.
You and I are going to have a baby.
Thanks to Allah.
My daylight... My sun...
My love.
The one who gives me strength with love.
You gave me such great news...
You gave me life.
When we save my father
...I swear we'll make
all the cruel ones kneel...
...and shake this world together.
I know.
Everything is possible with you.
Death is looming over Kayi.
Some ran away.
They are uneasy too.
What about the ones in the tribe?
What about my Ghazi?
Who knows how they are doing?
Brother... Ghazi was trained by you, Cerkutay.
He can beat even their best ones.
Don't worry, brother.
You and your son will come
together soon, God willing.
God willing.
I will sacrifice my life if I have
to but I'll take my son back.
But we need to find our Bey first.
Don't fall into despair but be patient.
We'll always carry our
grief in our hearts, but...
...we'll make Mongolians pay for this.
When Osman Bey is saved,
they all will burn in flames.
We'll make them pay for every
wound they opened inside us.
Cerkutay, check these trails. What is this?
Is it Osman Bey?
Brother, check this out.
Cart tracks... Still fresh.
There are also horses beside the cart.
The horse shoes were made
by Mongolian ironmongers.
It may be them.
Which way have they gone? We should follow.
This way, Bala Hatun.
-Come on then.
-Let's go, brother.
Let's go, alps!
Come on, come on! I'm coming, Osman.
Come on!
The fire is ready.
Meryem.
Here we go.
Take this. You bite this for the pain.
Well... This will hurt a lot.
But you need to endure.
I can endure, my Bey.
Press my hand if it goes wrong, alright?
Here we go. In the name of Allah,
the compassionate, the merciful.
Hold on, hold on.
Hang on!
Hang on, hang on! Hang on!
Look at me. Look.
I will cauterize it now.
It will hurt a lot. Worse
than any pain you know.
Here we go.
O Healer.
Hang on, girl. Hang on.
Well... You are....
You are so strong. Very strong.
It's obvious you're from these lands.
We don't know whose your parents are, but...
...I wish I knew them.
I wish.
I wish I did. If a cruel man hadn't killed them
..I would know them.
What about your father? Don't
you know anything about him?
Then..
...jackal...
...jackal..
...approached the gazelle...
...quietly, and said:
"Gazelle..
...do not wander around here...
Or else...
...they will abduct you."
He said "Come...
Let me take you to your house."
Did she go?
-No.
Little gazelle...
..was a bit afraid. She was afraid...
...but she was smart.
She said "No, no...
I will not come with you!"
Jackal, after hearing this...
...set his eyes on the gazelle!
Was she afraid? Was she alone?
The gazelle, yes she was afraid.
But deep in the forest...
...there was a wolf watching them. The wolf...
...would never let someone...
...hurt the gazelle.
The wolf..
...kept watching them.
The gazelle, who was scared, said:
O, the guardian of the forest!
Will you help me?
After hearing this, the wolf...
...leaped forward
Ssht...
"What is happening here?", he said...
"Where are you?", he said to the jackal.
After hearing this, the jackal
did not know what to do.
"No, no, no.", he said...
...and he started running away.
My Halime...
Did you lose your sleep again, my daughter?
She had her sleep...
But it ran away to the forest...
Did you find it?
Yes, we did. We did, right, my daughter?
Come on now, kiss your father. Kiss your father.
Isn't there another tale?
We heard enough tales.
Come, come here.
Come on.
The wolf protected the little gazelle...
Now it is time for the little
gazelle to sleep, my daughter.
Right, her father?
Sure, or else the jackal will follow her!
The jackal is coming, run, Halime!
Run, run
I'm coming! I'm coming! I'm coming!
My daughter...
The wolf..
...could not protect that gazelle.
Then the gazelle...
...turned into a bird and flew away.
So, you like shadow plays, huh, Meryem?
I don't know.
I do it sometimes.
I don't know why...
...but I feel happy when I do it.
It feels like...
...there was a moment long
ago when I was this happy.
There is a moment...
...that everyone feels happy.
How do you know so much about shadow plays?
My daughter...
...used to wait for her father every night.
She really loved shadow play.
She always waited for me to come and do it.
My daughter...
My Halime...
We lost her when she was so little...
If she...
...if she lived...
...she would probably be the same age as you.
Are you defending Osman right now, Poena?
The man who killed your mother and father..
...and left you alone between those bodies?
There is another cave ahead!
This horse... This is Osman's horse.
Be quiet.
Ohh my daughter...
You are carrying a big
burden at such a young age.
You don't have a family as well...
But their prayers will always protect you.
Besides...
...little gazelles...
...are never alone.
My daughter...
Blood, blood, blood...
Inform Ulugan.
Osman ran away but...
...Altuga caught him.
Tell him I will take him to Olcaytu. Go.
They found us. They want me.
You will stay here.
I can protect myself.
When I am here, I will protect you. Don't worry.
You will do as I say.
Osman
Blood blood blood!
You are trapped like a wounded wolf...
...but come out!
Come out Osman!
Don't be afraid, come!
Look, I know what they
want. They cannot kill me.
But they can kill you.
What about you...
What are you going to do, Osman Bey?
-Don't worry.
I will go out. I will waste their time.
But you...
Don't feel upset because you have no one.
Find Bala Hatun. You will run away while
I waste their time. She will protect you.
Come on now.
Blood! Blood! Blood!
You made us chase you, but again,
you are at the end of the way, Osman.
If a wolf does not make forty jackals howl
behind him, he cannot be called a wolf.
You have been running...
So you will die tired
I will take you to Olcaytu safely, but...
...I will break every bone in your body, Osman.
Nokers(Mongolian Soldiers),
break Osman's arms and legs separately!
Come on
God, why is this happening?
Why is my heart filled with worry?
Why do I want to help him?
Why?
If you lock the wolf...
..in a cage...
...you must take its swords.
You will cut off its claws.
You will tear out its teeth.
Otherwise, if you reach out your hand...
...it will rip off your arm.
Your daughter, Ilbay...
She gave a sword to the wolf.
And she became his hope.
My knights have spread out on both
sides of the Kayi Germiyan border.
Even if he escapes from that cage, he
won't be able to escape from our hands.
Do not forget we are talking about Osman, Lukas.
Since Bala and his Shahzades ran away from us...
...do not underestimate him.
We will catch them all Sofia.
Ulugan's nokers(Mongolian Soldiers)..
We are stronger.
It is in your best interest to
trust what this Hatun says.
For Osman Bey's insight is worth a thousand men.
You said he was your
Hatun's brother and let him in.
Ilbay...
Do you...
..trust him
I trust Yusuf Bey.
My brother pledged...
...allegiance to Ilbay Bey.
There is no need to discuss it, Ulugan.
Weren't you the ones...
...who pledged allegiance to Osman?
Trust doesn't fall from the sky.
It is gained.
Your brother will prove himself.
Nokers(Mongolian Soldiers)!
Bring the other Bey's son here!
You're exhausted Osman.
-You can't hold anymore.
-I will never seek mercy!
I will fight to the last drop of my blood.
-Come to me, dogs.
-Nokers(Mongolian Soldiers), you all attack!
Come to me.
Run away, girl.
You're not alone, huh?
Catch her and kill
We're here, Osman!
-Bala?
-We're here.
Attack!
-Cerkutay.
Say no more words.
No words to say. Only swords will speak now.
Here we go.
You dogs!
You took him captive but he's never alone!
I will make Ghazi a noker(Mongolian Soldier).
His life will belong to us.
-He won't be a rat like you.
-You think I'll leave my son to you?
I won't show mercy anymore
just because you are my brother.
My Bey!
Alps, Cerkutay.
May Allah give you a long life, my Bey.
Are you alright, my Bey?
We can provide what we lost.
If you live, the state will live.
Osman.
Are you alright?
-I'm good.
Are you good?
-How are you?
-Good. What did you do on your own?
Don't worry. I wasn't on my
own. Meryem was with me.
Meryem, what are you doing here?
You're wounded.
It's fine. Not a big deal.
I didn't want to just wait in the tribe.
I tracked them to help Osman Bey.
I was going to save his life
but he saved my life instead.
Praise be, my girl.
We don't know your parents but
obviously you have noble blood.
My Osman is alright. You are alright as well.
Even this dark night is enlightened for me.
-Well, Bala...
If your motherly attitude
is enough, we should go.
Osman.
Bala.
You never know what Altuga will do.
He's going to gather his men. We need to go.
Alright. But we need to let Orhan know first.
-They're near Sarical.
-Alright.
-Aykurt.
-My Bey.
Inform them quickly. We're going to the south.
We have a duty to perform and a battle to fight.
-Let's go.
As you order, my Bey.
Come on.
Get off! Get off!
Get off!
Why did you bring me here?
What do you want, dastards?
Yusuf, just like your treacherous sister...
...are you attempting treason?
Speak. What are you doing here?
Speak!
You are loyal to Osman Bey, huh?
For sure, you dog.
I'm loyal to Osman Bey, my
Shahzades and my state...
..to the end.
It's your turn, Yusuf.
Show me whose you are loyal to.
What a coincidence.
I wish I would kill you too.
Like your father Bayhan.
Don't mention my martyr father's
name with your filthy mouth again!
Come on.
Grab the dagger.
Do what the dog said, Yusuf!
If you don't, I swear...
..I will do the same to you.
Come on!
This took too long.
Take the dagger.
Come on.
-Come on!
-Yusuf.
Come on, brother.
Do it.
Come on!
You coward!
Good.
Commander Ulugan, Osman escaped.
He escaped?
I told you not to underestimate Osman!
We found his trails, commander.
Altuga must have captured him by now.
Lead the way.
Take me to him. Lead the way!
We've been riding since last night, my Bey.
-Our sons catch up soon, God willing.
-Don't worry, Bala.
-We'll get out of this trouble all together.
-Of course we will.
But I can't just swallow this, my Bey.
I was expecting Begum to do such a thing, but...
...what Ilbay did hurt me a lot.
We're being tested with our own kin.
Our destination is Ilah-i Kalimatullah.
So we won't show mercy
whoever stands against us.
My Bey, Ulugan and his nokers
(Mongolian Soldiers) are coming towards here.
They found our tracks.
Then we will make them
lose our tracks. Let's go!
Where is Osman?
I followed them all night. Commander Ulugan.
They've gone that way. We should hurry.
If you show such weakness again
...I will cut off
your head, Altuga.
Let's hunt the wolf.
They're going towards the south.
But nokers (Mongolian Soldiers)
must be looking for them too.
We should be careful.
Holofira.
-Are you alright?
-I'm fine.
-It's nothing. Don't worry.
-My Holofira.
You say you're fine...
...but your eyes look pale.
Don't be stubborn.
Go to Ulgen Hatun and have some rest.
No, Orhan.
If I don't stand beside you now, the
bed I'm lying on will swallow me like mud.
Your presence gives me strength.
We will go meet Osman Bey together.
-Tell her something. Alaaddin.
-Holofira is strong, brother.
It's better she stays with you...
...instead of going reluctantly
and worrying about you.
-Alaaddin.
-Orhan Bey.
I told you on the way.
I will look after Holofira's two lives.
Don't be worrying, brother.
Fine. Fine.
Let's go.
You go first, hatuns.
Come on, come on.
You traitors.
Wherever you
...you can't run away from me, Osman.
Not this time, Osman.
You can't run off this time.
They've surrounded us.
This is it, Bala!
Nobody can save you from me now!
You say so?
I will come back for all of you.
Then you will beg me
But I will show no mercy..
..for any of you.
We're drawing back.
Go wherever you want.
Where you will end up in
the end is Olcaytu Khan's feet.
Red Woman, you stay here with me.
We never know what evil
things Lukas and you can do.
Let's go!
We can't ride on. We have to go on foot.
Meryem, Bala. You go first.
This is the end, Osman.
We're trapped.
My Bey, we clear the way. You should just go.
Stay behind me.
I will kill you before Ulugan arrives.
Someone's coming. Take your positions.
Look, look.
While I was looking for the
father, Tengri offered me his baby!
What you're chasing...
...is only your death, vile dog.
Ilbay.
Begum Hatun.
-You...
-Yes!
-Call us the new masters of Kayi!
-What are you talking about?
You joined us to wait for
the day when you'd bite, huh?
I swear you'll pay for your treason!
Listen to me carefully, Ulugan.
You and those dastards with you...
...you will all die by our swords.
The sword of justice of Osman
Bey who you tried to kill...
...will...
...surely cut your head off.
Don't worry, Osman's dog.
Until Olcaytu Khan wants Osman to die...
...he will live in my chains.
But death is the only way for you.
If we die, we'll become martyrs, if you
die, you'll just become corpses, you dog!
Come on!
Draw your sword!
Orhan, there are too many of them.
I will kill you with my own sword!
Now your era is over!
I will burn and destroy your lands and borders!
Know this..
Only my sword determines
the borders on these lands.
Do you have the courage, huh? Do you? Face me!
It's been a long time since I
ripped your heart out, Osman.
We hurt you in such a way that...
...you didn't even notice it.
Your grandchild.
Alaeddin's baby...
I killed it in Gonca's womb.
What?
Did you kill my grandchild?
Did you kill
Did you kill?
I swear..
I swear.
I swear on this world...
...while you die...
...you will ask for my forgiveness.
You will beg me, you dog!
You will answer me today!
I will kill you all.
This land is my land!
If we're not destined to walk on it,
we know how to lie under it as well.
If your preaching is over, I will be
finishing the short epic you wrote, Osman.
No, you are wrong.
My epic is just beginning.
Come, you dog!
Now you have no breath to take.
You ruled with blood, and you
will pay the price with your life.
Not this time, Osman!
You will pay the price this time.
Soldiers! Kill Bala and the girl!
Meryem
Meryem!
Meryem! Hold my hand! Give me your hand, Meryem!
Bala!
Hold my hand, my daughter!
Osman!
Come on! Go!
Your Hatun is calling you! You cannot go...
Because you are all alone, Osman
You are all alone!
I am not strong enough,
Bala Hatun. I cannot do it...
Hold me... Here. I got it.
-I cannot...
I will not let you go. I will not.
Please, don't...
Alright, my daughter.I
am here. It will be alright.
Meryem, don't look down! Look at me!
Bala Hatun, I am too tired!
Osman.
Where are you going Osman?
You were going to make me pay the price!
Your era is over!
Now we will rule!
Even if everyone turns into a jackal...
...I will always be the lone wolf.
I never knelt before someone! And
I will never kneel before someone!
Meryem no! No, Meryem! Come on Meryem!
Come on, Osman!